<ModMetaData>
	<name>Vanilla Textures Expanded - Genetic Rim</name>
	<author>Oskar Potocki, Sarg Bjornson, Luizi</author>
	<supportedVersions>
     
      <li>1.1</li>
	  <li>1.2</li>
   </supportedVersions>
    <modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>sarg.geneticrim</packageId>
			<displayName>Genetic Rim</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1113137502</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/juanosarg/GeneticRim/releases</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>sarg.geneticrim</li>
		
	</loadAfter>
	<packageId>VanillaExpanded.VTEXGR</packageId>
	<description>&lt;size=24&gt;Features&lt;/size&gt;
Vanilla Textures Expanded - Genetic Rim is a full-scale overhaul of Genetic Rim textures, with its main aim being improving the quality of the artwork and make it more in-line with textures of Vanilla game and Vanilla Expanded mod series. 

This texture pack includes over 550 textures remade in vector-based software (same method used for Vanilla Expanded mods and vanilla game), exported into higher resolution for a cleaner, more sophisticated outcome.

When redrawing the Genetic Rim textures, our main focus was on keeping them consistent with what players are used to - We only applied drastic changes to artworks that weren’t as logical or aesthetically pleasing. The way we did it, is we analyzed the animals that create a given mutation, and then applied their traits onto a new creature.

&lt;size=24&gt;Issues&lt;/size&gt;
Giddy-Up Saddles in some creatures will need to be redone from scratch. This will be worked on at a later date, since it is a ton of work

&lt;size=24&gt;Plans for the future&lt;/size&gt;
- Textures for the Dinosauria, Megafauna, and Alpha Animals patches redone

&lt;size=24&gt;Compatibility&lt;/size&gt;
Since this is a texture mod it should be compatible with almost everything



&lt;size=24&gt;Changelog&lt;/size&gt;
v1.6: Added Megafauna patch animals (01/04/21)
v1.5: Added Dinosauria patch animals (31/03/21)
v1.4: Added Alpha Animals patch animals (30/03/21)
v1.3: Added graphics for items for all GR patches (16/10/20)
v1.2: Updated for RimWorld 1.2 (11/08/20)
v1.1: Added graphics for the Cosmic Horrors Patch (16/06/20)
v1.0: Release (23/05/20)


		</description>
</ModMetaData>
